import { quizQuestions } from '../types/quiz'
export const iplquestionlist: quizQuestions[] = [
    {
        question: 'Who is the first Indian to score a hundred in the IPL? ',
        options: ['Paul Valthaty', 'Manish Pandey', 'Gautam Gambhir', 'Virender Sehwag'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Who captained the Kolkata Knight Riders to the IPL title in 2012? ',
        options: ['Brendon McCullum', 'Sourav Ganguly', 'Dinesh Karthik', 'Gautam Gambhir'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Who won the Man of the Match award in the IPL 2008 final?',
        options: ['Shane Warne', 'MS Dhoni', 'Shane Watson', 'Yusuf Pathan'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the first player to feature in 200 IPL games? ',
        options: ['MS Dhoni', 'Virat Kohli', 'Suresh Raina', 'Rohit Sharma'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Before 2020, in which year did a part of the IPL take place in the UAE?',
        options: ['2012', '2013', '2014', '2015'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the highest individual score for a batsman in the IPL?',
        options: ['175*', '170*', '169*', '158*'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Who among the following has NOT won the Purple Cap so far?',
        options: ['RP Singh', 'Dwayne Bravo', 'Imran Tahir', 'Amit Mishra'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which team did former Pakistan player Misbah-ul-Haq represent in IPL 2008?',
        options: ['Kolkata Knight Riders', 'Deccan Chargers', 'Mumbai Indians', 'Royal Challengers Bangalore'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'In which season did Virat Kohli score all his IPL centuries? ',
        options: ['IPL 2013', 'IPL 2014', 'IPL 2016', 'IPL 2019'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Against which team were the most centuries scored in IPL 2018? ',
        options: ['Mumbai Indians', 'Rajasthan Royals', 'Sunrisers Hyderabad', 'Kolkata Knight Riders'],
        answer: 3
    }
];